<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

<!--  CHAPTER NAMES  -->

    <string-array name="chapter_names">
        <item>Whole Numbers</item>
        <item>Word Problems</item>
        <item>Decimals</item>
        <item>Fractions</item>
        <item>Ratio and Proportion</item>
        <item>Percent</item>
        <item>Measurement</item>
        <item>Data Analysis, Statistics, and Probability</item>
        <item>Basic Geometry</item>
        <item>The Basics of Algebra</item>
        <item>Advanced Topics in Algebra and Geometry</item>
    </string-array>

<!--  SUBTOPIC NAMES  -->

    <string-array name="subtopic_names_1">
        <item>Whole Number Definition</item>
        <item>Place Value</item>
        <item>Arithmetic Facts</item>
        <item>The Basic Operations</item>
        <item>Shortcuts: Rounding and Estimating</item>
        <item>Mean and Median</item>
        <item>Exponents and Square Roots</item>
        <item>Number Sequences and Patterns</item>
        <item>Properties of Numbers</item>
        <item>Order of Operations</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="subtopic_content_1">
        <item><b>Whole Numbers </b>can be written with the digits 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, and 9, and are divisible by 1 with no remainder. </item>
        <item><b>Place Value: </b>In our decimal number system, the value of a digit depends on its place, or position, in the number. Each place has a value of 10 times the place to its right.
            \n\n A number written in \"standard form\" is separated into groups of three digits using commas, for easier readability. Each of these groups is called a period.
            \n\n The idea of place value is at the heart of our number system. First, however, a symbol for nothing —our zero— had to be invented. Zero \"holds the place\" for a particular value, when no other digit goes in that position. For example, the number \"100\" in words means one hundred, no tens, and no ones. Without a symbol for nothing, our decimal number system wouldn\'t work.
            \n\n Beginning with the ones place at the right, each place value is multiplied by increasing powers of 10. For example, the value of the first place on the right is \"one\", the value of the place to the left of it is \"ten,\" which is 10 times 1. The place to the left of the tens place is hundreds, which is 10 times 10, and so forth.
        </item>
        <item>These are some definitions that you need to know for the GED: \n
            <ul>
                \n\n\t&#8226;    The answer to an addition problem is called the <b><u>sum</u></b>. For example, in the problem
                    <b>9 + 5 = 14</b>, <b>14</b> is the <b>sum</b> of 9 and 5.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    The answer to a multiplication problem is called the <b><u>product</u></b>. For example, in the problem
                    <b>9 * 5 = 45</b>, <b>45</b> is the <b>product</b> of 9 and 5.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    <b>Whole numbers</b> include 0 and all <b>positive</b> numbers. A <b>positive</b> number is any number
                    greater than 0.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    An <b>odd</b> number is defined as not evenly divisible by 2. The units digit of an odd number will always be 1, 3, 5, 7, or 9.
                    For example: 9, 47, and 2,400,513 are all odd numbers. The numbers 6 and 538 are not.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    An <b>even</b> number is defined as being evenly divisible by 2. The units digit of an even number has to be 0, 2, 4, 6, or 8.
                    For example: 4, 52, and 386 are all even numbers. The numbers 3 and 423 are not.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    <b>Consecutive numbers</b> are one after the other. For example, 12, 13, and 14 are consecutive numbers. Also, the next three consecutive odd numbers
                    following 13 are 15, 17, 19.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    A <b>prime</b> number is only evenly divisible by itself and 1. For example, 17 is a prime number because
                    the only numbers that divide evenly into 17 are 17 and 1. However, 15 is not a prime number because aside from
                    15 and 1, 15 is also evenly divisible by 3 and 5.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    A <b>factor</b> is another word for divisor. A factor is a number that divides evenly into another number. For example,
                    5 is <b>a factor of</b> 15, and <b>the factors of</b> 12 are 1, 2, 3, 4, and 6.
            </ul>\n
        </item>
        <item>The four basic operations in arithmetic are <b>addition, subtraction, multiplication,</b> and <b>division</b>. Read more about each below, and watch the animation for a step-by-step example of each.
            <ul>
                \n\n\t&#8226;    <b>Addition: </b>The answer to an addition problem is called the <b>sum</b>, or <b>total</b>. The symbol for an addition operation is the <b>+</b> sign.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    <b>Subtraction: </b>The answer to a subtraction problem is called the <b>difference</b>. The symbol for the subtraction operation is the <b>-</b> sign. To find the difference between two numbers, you should put the larger number on top.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    <b>Multiplication: </b>The answer to a multiplication problem is called the <b>product</b>. The <b>x</b> sign and the <b>*</b>, as well as a raised dot between two numbers, and numbers in parentheses with no signs in between all symbolize a multiplication operation.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    <b>Division: </b>The answer to a division problem is called the <b>quotient</b>. The <b>&#x00F7;</b> sign, the <b>&#x27CC;</b> sign, and a slash all symbolize a division operation.
            </ul>\n
        </item>
        <item><b>Estimating</b> is an important part of mathematics and a very handy tool for everyday life. Get in the habit of estimating amounts of money, lengths of time, distances, and many other physical quantities.
            \n\nRounding off is a kind of estimating.
            \n\n\n<b>3 STEPS To round off whole numbers:</b>
            <ul>
                \n\n\t&#8226; Find the place value you want (the \"rounding digit\") and look to the digit just to the right of it.
                \n\n\t&#8226; If that digit is less than 5, do not change the \"rounding digit\" but change all digits to the right of the \"rounding digit\" to zero.
                \n\n\t&#8226; If that digit is greater than or equal to 5, add one to the rounding digit and change all digits to the right of the rounding digit to zero.
            </ul>
            \n\n\nTo round a number you must first find the rounding digit, or the digit occupying the place value you\'re rounding to. Then look at the digit to the right of the rounding digit. If it is less than 5, then leave the rounding digit unchanged.
            If it is more than five, add one to the rounding digit. If it is five, the rule is to always round up (add one to the rounding digit). This rule was created to \"break the tie\" when you are rounding a number that is exactly between two other numbers.
            These kinds of rules are called \"conventions\", and are important so we all get the same answer when doing the same problems.
            \n\nIf you\'re dealing with a whole number, all the digits to the right of the rounding digit become zero.
        </item>
        <item>For a set of numbers, the \"mean\" is a number that represents those numbers. The term \"mean\" is another word for the \"average\" of a set of numbers.
            \n\n RULE:
                \n\n\t&#8226; To find the mean of a set of numbers, add all of the numbers in the set, and then divide the sum by the size of the set (the number of numbers in the set).
            \n\nA \"median\" of a set of numbers is the number in the middle of a group of numbers. Half of the numbers in a set are greater than the median, and half are less than the median.
            \n\n RULE:
            \n\n\t&#8226; To find the median for a group of numbers, first arrange the numbers in order from smallest to largest. If there is an odd number of numbers in the set, then the middle number is the median. If there is an even number of numbers in the set,
            then the median is the mean (or average) of the two numbers in the middle.
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Exponents: </b>
            \n\nExponents are a shorthand way to show how many times a number, called the base, is multiplied times itself. A number with an exponent is said to be \"raised to the power\" of that exponent.
            \n\nAn exponent tells you how many times the base number is used as a factor. A base of five raised to the second power is called \"five squared\" and means \"five times five.\" Five raised to the third power is called \"five cubed\" and means \"five times five times five.\"
            The base can be any sort of number: a whole number, a decimal number, or a fraction can all be raised to a power.
            \n\n<b>RULES: </b>
                \n\n\t&#8226;    To find a power, write out the base number as many times as the exponent indicates, then multiply.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    Any base number raised to the power of one equals that base number.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    1 raised to any power equals 1.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    Any number raised to the power of zero equals 1.
            \n\n<b>Square Roots: </b>
            \n\nFinding the square root of a number is the inverse operation of squaring that number. Remember, the square of a number is that number times itself.
            \n\nMany mathematical operations have an inverse, or opposite, operation. Subtraction is the opposite of addition, division is the inverse of multiplication, and so on. Squaring, which we learned about in a previous lesson (exponents), has an inverse too, called "finding the square root." Remember, the square of a number is that number times itself.
            \n\nThe perfect squares are the squares of the whole numbers: 1, 4, 9, 16, 25, 36, 49, 64, 81, 100 ... Square roots of non-perfect numbers can be found using a calculator, or other methods.
            \n\nTo find the square root of a number, you ask yourself \"What number multiplied by itself equals this number?\"
        </item>
        <item>A <b>number sequence</b>, also called a <b>number series</b>, is a list of numbers in a specific order or pattern.
        \n\nThe numbers 1,2,3,4,5,6,7.... form the most familiar number sequence, and the number 8 is called the next <b>term</b> in the sequence.
        \n\n<b>On the GED you may be asked to find the missing number or the next term in a sequence. To do so, follow these steps: </b>
            \n\n\t&#8226;   Find the pattern that changes the numbers from left to right
            \n\n\t&#8226;   Continue this pattern to find the missing number
        </item>
        <item>
            We use the following properties, or characteristics, of numbers that you will need to understand how to use in order to solve math problems.

            \n\n<b>Commutative Property of Addition:</b>
            \n\n\t<b>a + b = b + a</b>
            \n\nThe commutative property of addition says that we can add numbers in any order. You can remember the commutative property by thinking of the numbers \"commuting,\" or changing places. The example shows us that
            \"negative two plus positive four\" is the same as \"positive four plus negative two.\"

            \n\n<b>Commutative Property of Multiplication: </b>
            \n\n\t<b>ab = ba</b>
            \n\nThe commutative property of multiplication is very similar. It says that we can multiply numbers in any order we want without changing the result. The example shows us that \"negative two times positive four\" is
            the same as \"positive four times negative two.\"

            \n\n<b>Associative Property of Addition: </b>
            \n\n\t<b>(a + b) + c = a + (b + c)</b>
            \n\nThe associative property of addition tells us that we can group numbers in a sum in any way we want and still get the same answer. You can remember the associative property by thinking of two numbers
            associating with each other, and then one leaves to associate with another number.

            \n\n<b>Associative Property of Multiplication: </b>
            \n\n\t<b>(ab)c = a(bc)</b>
            \n\nThe associative property of multiplication tells us that we can group numbers in a product in any way we want and still get the same answer.

            \n\n<b>Distributive Property: </b>
            \n\n\t<b>a(b + c) = ab + bc</b>
            \n\nThe distributive property comes into play when an expression involving addition is then multiplied by something. It tells us that we can add first and then multiply, or multiply first and then add.
            Either way, the multiplication is \"distributed\" over all the terms inside the parentheses.
        </item>
        <item>When expressions have more than one operation, we have to follow rules for the order of operations:
            \n\n\t&#8226;    First, do operations inside grouping symbols
            \n\n\t&#8226;    Next, do all work with powers (exponents and square roots) from left to right
            \n\n\t&#8226;    Next, do multiplication or division operations from left to right
            \n\n\t&#8226;    Last, do addition or subtraction operations from left to right
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_1">
        <item>
            <ul>
                \n\n\t&#8226;    27 <b>IS</b> a Whole Number
                \n\n\t&#8226;    3 1/2 <b>IS NOT</b> a Whole Number.
            </ul>\n
        </item>
        <item>Numbers can be represented in many ways, but standard form is usually the easiest and shortest way. Here are some numbers expressed in different forms, with their standard form shown alongside\n\n
            <ul>
                \n\n\t&#8226;    one billion, sixty million, five hundred twenty thousand             1,060,520,000
                \n\n\t&#8226;    four hundred sixteen thousand, seven hundred thirty-one             416,731
                \n\n\t&#8226;    6,000,000 + 70,000 + 20 + 1             6,070,021
            </ul>\n
            \n\n In each of these numbers, what value does the digit 5 have? \n\n
            <ul>
                \n\n\t&#8226;    In 17,526,010 the 5 represents <b>five hundred thousands</b>
                \n\n\t&#8226;    In 2,110,735,000 the 5 represents <b>five thousands</b>
            </ul>\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <ul>
                \n\n\t&#8226;    List the first three consecutive odd numbers following 19:          <b>21, 23, 25</b>
                \n\n\t&#8226;    List the three prime factors of 35:           <b>1, 5, 7</b>
            </ul>\n
        </item>
        <item>ANIMATION</item>
        <item>To round 7,350 to the nearest hundred:/n/n
            <ul>
                \n\n\t&#8226;    Find the rounding digit, 3.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    Look at the digit to the right of the three, 5.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    Since 7,350 is exactly halfway between 7,300 and 7,400, the two nearest multiples of one hundred, we need the rule to decide which way to round.
                \n\n\t&#8226;    The rule says you round up, so the answer is 7,400.
            </ul>\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <ul>Find the mean of 10, 18, 37, and 24:
                \n\n\t&#8226;    First find the sum of the four numbers: \n\n\t\t 10 + 18 + 37 + 23 = 88
                \n\n\t&#8226;    Divide the sum by 4, the number of numbers in the set: \n\n\t\t 88 &#x00F7; 4 = 22
                \n\n\t&#8226;    The mean (or average) of the set of numbers is 22.
            </ul>

        </item>
        <item>Powers</item>
        <item>sq, num seq</item>
        <item>
            <b>Commutative Property of Addition:</b>
            \n\n\t&#8226;    -2 + 4 = 4 + (-2)
            \n\nThe example shows us that \"negative two plus positive four\" is the same as \"positive four plus negative two.\"

            \n\n<b>Commutative Property of Multiplication:</b>
            \n\n\t&#8226;    -2(4) = 4(-2)
            \n\nThe example shows us that \"negative two times positive four\" is the same as \"positive four times negative two.\"

            \n\n<b>Associative Property of Addition:</b>
            \n\n\t&#8226;    (-2 + 4) + 3 = -2 + (4 + 3)
            \n\nThe example shows us that we can either add \"negative two and positive four\" together and then add that sum to positive three
            to get the final answer, or we can add \"positive four and positive three\" together first and then add that sum to negative two to get the final answer.
            The answer will be the same no matter which way we do it

            \n\n<b>Associative Property of Multiplication: </b>
            \n\n\t&#8226;    (-2 x 4) x 3 = -2 (4 x 3)
            \n\nThe example shows us that we can either multiply \"negative two and positive four\" together and then multiply that product times positive three to get the final answer,
            or we can multiply \"positive four and positive three\" together first and then multiply that product times negative two to get the final answer. The answer will be the same no matter which way we do it.

            \n\n<b>Distributive Property: </b>
            \n\n\t&#8226;    -2(4 + 3) = -2(4) + -2(3)
            \n\nIn the example, we can either add the numbers inside the parentheses first (4 + 3), and then multiply the result by -2; OR, we can multiply the -2 and each term separately and then add the two products together. The answer is the same in both cases.
        </item>
        <item>ex</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_1">
        <item>McGraw-Hill\'s GED Mathematics Study Program</item>
        <item>Math.com</item>
        <item>McGraw-Hill\'s GED Mathematics Study Program</item>
        <item>McGraw-Hill\'s GED Mathematics Study Program</item>
        <item>Math.com</item>
        <item>McGraw-Hill\'s GED Mathematics Study Program</item>
        <item>Math.com</item>
        <item>McGraw-Hill\'s GED Mathematics Study Program</item>
        <item>Math.com</item>
        <item>Math.com</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="questions_1">
        <item>What is 7488 divided by 18?</item>
        <item>Find the difference between 905,246 and 387,529</item>
        <item>34,510 + 97,286 = ?</item>
        <item>Find the difference between 32,070 and 9,958</item>
        <item>What is the quotient of 666 divided by 18?</item>
        <item>Find the product of 6000 and 58</item>
        <item>81,206 – 7,395 = ?</item>
        <item>356 x 48 = ?</item>
        <item>What is the difference between 2,309,000 and 586,900?</item>
        <item>79 + 3148 + 307 = ?</item>
        <item>What is the product of 58 and 37 rounded to the nearest hundred?</item>
        <item>30,550/650 = ?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="answers_1">
        <item>416</item>
        <item>517,717</item>
        <item>131,796</item>
        <item>22,112</item>
        <item>37</item>
        <item>348,000</item>
        <item>73,811</item>
        <item>17,088</item>
        <item>1,722,100</item>
        <item>3534</item>
        <item>2100</item>
        <item>47</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="subtopic_names_2">
        <item>Steps to Solving Word Problems</item>
        <item>GED Problem Solving</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="subtopic_content_2">
        <item>
            Use these five steps to work through word problems:\n
            <ul>
                \n\n&#8226;Step 1:    Understand the question: what is it asking for?
                \n\nIt is important to have a clear understanding of what the question is asking for in order to move forward with solving a word problem. One strategy to help with this is to try to put the question into your own words in your head, and visualize the problem.
                \n\n&#8226;Step 2:    Determine what information you are going to need to answer the question.
                \n\nSometimes word problems on the GED contain more information than is necessary to solve the problem. For example, the problem could contain an extra number that is never used in the operations to solve the problem. It is important to take this second step to determine what information is relevant to answering the question you determined in step 1.
                \nSome word problems will have an answer choice that says \"Not enough information is given\". Be very careful in choosing this answer, and make sure that the question can not be answered with the information that is given.
                \n\n&#8226;Step 3:    Choose the arithmetic operation(s) you need to perform: addition, subtraction, multiplication, or division?
                \n\nFor this step, make sure you read the problem carefully in order to determine the correct operation to use. There are important clues in the wording of the question, and in this section we will go over some common terms that indicate each operation.
                \n\nAddition: The words \"sum\", \"total\", \"combined\", and \"altogether\" suggest that addition should be used.
                \n\tExample: Anna makes $250 a week, and her mother makes $310 a week. What is their combined income each week?
                \n\nSubtraction: The phrases \"How much more?\", \"How much less?\", \"How much greater\", \"How much smaller\", \"Find the difference\", and \"Find the balance\" all suggest that subtraction should be used.
                \n\tExample: The maximum capacity of an elevator in an apartment building is 2500 pounds. A person weighing 185 pounds gets in. How much more weight can the elevator hold?
                \n\nMultiplication: A word problem could give you information about one thing, and ask you to calculate an amount for several things, which suggests that multiplication should be used. For example, rates such as \"dollars per pound\", \"dollars per hour\", \"miles per gallon\", or \"rent per month\" could be used.
                \n\tExample: If Ben can drive 34 miles with 1 gallon of gas, how far can he drive with 5 gallons of gas?
                \n\nDivision: A problem might give you information for several things, and ask you to calculate an amount for one thing, which suggests that division should be used. Notice that this is the opposite of the typical structure for a multiplication word problem.
                \n\tExample: If Carrie pays $7,200 per year in rent for her apartment, what is her monthly rent?
                \n\n&#8226;Step 4:    Solve the problem, and remember to check your work.
                \n\nFor this step, your skills in basic arithmetic operations are very important. To brush up on these skills, refer to Section 1.4 to review. Make sure that you do your math neatly and accurately, and double check your computation work for this step.
                \n\n&#8226;Step 5:    Double check that you answered the question you determined in step 1, and that your answer makes sense in context.
                \n\nFor this step, make sure that your answer is a reasonable answer to the question being asked, in context. Use common sense, and you can even use estimation to make sure that your answer is logical.
            </ul>\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Multistep Problems:
            \n\n\tWord problems may require you to perform more than one operation to get to the solution. Think about each individual step carefully, and make sure to be just as accurate with each step because each part of a multistep problem must be correct to reach the correct solution.
            \n\n
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_2">
        <item>
            Question: Bob cuts grass for 20 hours every week, making $11 an hour. How much money does he make each week?\n
            \n\n\t&#8226;Step 1:    What is being asked: How much money does Bob make each week?
            \n\n\t&#8226;Step 2:    Information needed: 15 hours each week, $11 per hour
            \n\n\t&#8226;Step 3:    Arithmetic Operations: He makes $11 per hour, for 15 hours each week, so the operation is multiplying.
            \n\n\t&#8226;Step 4:    Solve: 20 hours x $11 = $220
            \n\n\t&#8226;Step 5:    Make sure it makes sense: $220 is a logical amount of money to make each week for a part time job cutting grass, so it does make sense. The original question, how much does he make in a week, was answered.
        </item>
        <item>
            Multistep Problem Example:
            \n\nIrene works 30 hours per week at a job making $11 an hour. She has a second job at which she works 10 hours per week making $8 an hour. Altogether, how much money does Irene make each week from her two jobs?
            \n\n\t&#8226;Step 1:    Find how much she makes each week from her first job: Multiply the hours worked per week by the hourly pay rate, 30 x 11 = $330.
            \n\n\t&#8226;Step 2:    Find how much she makes each week at her second job: Multiply the hours worked per week by the hourly pay rate, 10 x 8 = $80.
            \n\n\t&#8226;Step 3:    Add the two products: 330 + 80 = $410.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_2">
        <item>McGraw-Hill\'s GED Mathematics Study Program</item>
        <item>GED Problem Solving</item>
    </string-array>





    <string-array name="subtopic_names_3">
        <item>Decimals Introduction</item>
        <item>Understanding Decimals</item>
        <item>Adding and Subtracting Decimals</item>
        <item>Multiplying and Dividing Decimals</item>
        <item>Scientific Notation with Large Numbers</item>
        <item>Decimal Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="subtopic_content_3">
        <item>The zero and the counting numbers (1,2,3,...) make up the set of whole numbers. But not every number is a whole number. Our decimal system lets us write numbers of all types and sizes, using a clever symbol called the decimal point.
        \n\nAs you move right from the decimal point, each place value is divided by 10.
        </item>
        <item>
            Our decimal system of numbers lets us write numbers as large or as small as we want, using a secret weapon called the decimal point. In our number system, digits can be placed to the left and right of a decimal point, to indicate numbers greater than one or less than one. The decimal point helps us to keep track of where the \"ones\" place is.
            It\'s placed just to the right of the ones place. As we move right from the decimal point, each number place is divided by 10.
            \n\nWe can read the decimal number 127.578 as \"one hundred twenty seven and five hundred seventy-eight thousandths\". But in daily life, we\'d usually read it as \"one hundred twenty seven point five seven eight.\"
        </item>
        <item>Adding and Subtracting Decimals</item>
        <item>Multiplying and Dividing Decimals</item>
        <item>Scientific Notation with Large Numbers</item>
        <item>Decimal Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_3">
        <item>Understanding Decimals</item>
        <item>Adding and Subtracting Decimals</item>
        <item>Multiplying and Dividing Decimals</item>
        <item>Scientific Notation with Large Numbers</item>
        <item>Decimal Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_3">
        <item>Understanding Decimals</item>
        <item>Adding and Subtracting Decimals</item>
        <item>Multiplying and Dividing Decimals</item>
        <item>Scientific Notation with Large Numbers</item>
        <item>Decimal Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="subtopic_names_4">
        <item>Understanding Fractions</item>
        <item>Working with Fractions</item>
        <item>Adding Fractions</item>
        <item>Subtracting Fractions</item>
        <item>Multiplying Fractions</item>
        <item>Dividing Fractions</item>
        <item>Fractions and Decimals</item>
        <item>Scientific Notation with Small Numbers</item>
        <item>Fraction Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="subtopic_content_4">
        <item>Understanding Fractions</item>
        <item>Working with Fractions</item>
        <item>Adding Fractions</item>
        <item>Subtracting Fractions</item>
        <item>Multiplying Fractions</item>
        <item>Dividing Fractions</item>
        <item>Fractions and Decimals</item>
        <item>Scientific Notation with Small Numbers</item>
        <item>Fraction Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_4">
        <item>Understanding Fractions</item>
        <item>Working with Fractions</item>
        <item>Adding Fractions</item>
        <item>Subtracting Fractions</item>
        <item>Multiplying Fractions</item>
        <item>Dividing Fractions</item>
        <item>Fractions and Decimals</item>
        <item>Scientific Notation with Small Numbers</item>
        <item>Fraction Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_4">
        <item>Understanding Fractions</item>
        <item>Working with Fractions</item>
        <item>Adding Fractions</item>
        <item>Subtracting Fractions</item>
        <item>Multiplying Fractions</item>
        <item>Dividing Fractions</item>
        <item>Fractions and Decimals</item>
        <item>Scientific Notation with Small Numbers</item>
        <item>Fraction Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>





    <string-array name="subtopic_names_5">
        <item>Ratio</item>
        <item>Proportion</item>
        <item>Proportion Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="subtopic_content_5">
        <item>Ratio</item>
        <item>Proportion</item>
        <item>Proportion Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_5">
        <item>Ratio</item>
        <item>Proportion</item>
        <item>Proportion Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_5">
        <item>Ratio</item>
        <item>Proportion</item>
        <item>Proportion Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>




    <string-array name="subtopic_names_6">
        <item>Understanding Percent</item>
        <item>Percents, Decimals, and Fractions</item>
        <item>Solving Percent Problems</item>
        <item>Percent Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="subtopic_content_6">
        <item>Understanding Percent</item>
        <item>Percents, Decimals, and Fractions</item>
        <item>Solving Percent Problems</item>
        <item>Percent Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_6">
        <item>Understanding Percent</item>
        <item>Percents, Decimals, and Fractions</item>
        <item>Solving Percent Problems</item>
        <item>Percent Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_6">
        <item>Understanding Percent</item>
        <item>Percents, Decimals, and Fractions</item>
        <item>Solving Percent Problems</item>
        <item>Percent Word Problems</item>
    </string-array>






    <string-array name="subtopic_names_7">
        <item>Customary Measures</item>
        <item>Metric Measures</item>
        <item>Converting Measurements</item>
        <item>Scales, Meters, and Gauges</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="subtopic_content_7">
        <item>Customary Measures</item>
        <item>Metric Measures</item>
        <item>Converting Measurements</item>
        <item>Scales, Meters, and Gauges</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_7">
        <item>Customary Measures</item>
        <item>Metric Measures</item>
        <item>Converting Measurements</item>
        <item>Scales, Meters, and Gauges</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_7">
        <item>Customary Measures</item>
        <item>Metric Measures</item>
        <item>Converting Measurements</item>
        <item>Scales, Meters, and Gauges</item>
    </string-array>




    <string-array name="subtopic_names_8">
        <item>Graphs and Tables</item>
        <item>Probability</item>
        <item>Statistical Analysis</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="subtopic_content_8">
        <item>Graphs and Tables</item>
        <item>Probability</item>
        <item>Statistical Analysis</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_8">
        <item>Graphs and Tables</item>
        <item>Probability</item>
        <item>Statistical Analysis</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_8">
        <item>Graphs and Tables</item>
        <item>Probability</item>
        <item>Statistical Analysis</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="subtopic_names_9">
        <item>Common Geometric Shapes</item>
        <item>Perimeter and Circumference</item>
        <item>Area</item>
        <item>Solid Figures</item>
        <item>Volume</item>
        <item>Triangles</item>
        <item>Similarity and Congruence</item>
        <item>Pythagorean Relationship</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="subtopic_content_9">
        <item>Common Geometric Shapes</item>
        <item>Perimeter and Circumference</item>
        <item>Area</item>
        <item>Solid Figures</item>
        <item>Volume</item>
        <item>Triangles</item>
        <item>Similarity and Congruence</item>
        <item>Pythagorean Relationship</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_9">
        <item>Common Geometric Shapes</item>
        <item>Perimeter and Circumference</item>
        <item>Area</item>
        <item>Solid Figures</item>
        <item>Volume</item>
        <item>Triangles</item>
        <item>Similarity and Congruence</item>
        <item>Pythagorean Relationship</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_9">
        <item>Common Geometric Shapes</item>
        <item>Perimeter and Circumference</item>
        <item>Area</item>
        <item>Solid Figures</item>
        <item>Volume</item>
        <item>Triangles</item>
        <item>Similarity and Congruence</item>
        <item>Pythagorean Relationship</item>
    </string-array>





    <string-array name="subtopic_names_10">
        <item>Working with Signed Numbers</item>
        <item>Simplifying Algebraic Expressions</item>
        <item>Solving One-Step Equations</item>
        <item>Solving Longer Equations</item>
        <item>Solving Inequalities</item>
        <item>Writing Algebraic Expressions</item>
        <item>Using Algebra to Solve Word Problems</item>
        <item>Using Algebra to Solve Geometry Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="subtopic_content_10">
        <item>Working with Signed Numbers</item>
        <item>Simplifying Algebraic Expressions</item>
        <item>Solving One-Step Equations</item>
        <item>Solving Longer Equations</item>
        <item>Solving Inequalities</item>
        <item>Writing Algebraic Expressions</item>
        <item>Using Algebra to Solve Word Problems</item>
        <item>Using Algebra to Solve Geometry Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_10">
        <item>Working with Signed Numbers</item>
        <item>Simplifying Algebraic Expressions</item>
        <item>Solving One-Step Equations</item>
        <item>Solving Longer Equations</item>
        <item>Solving Inequalities</item>
        <item>Writing Algebraic Expressions</item>
        <item>Using Algebra to Solve Word Problems</item>
        <item>Using Algebra to Solve Geometry Problems</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_10">
        <item>Working with Signed Numbers</item>
        <item>Simplifying Algebraic Expressions</item>
        <item>Solving One-Step Equations</item>
        <item>Solving Longer Equations</item>
        <item>Solving Inequalities</item>
        <item>Writing Algebraic Expressions</item>
        <item>Using Algebra to Solve Word Problems</item>
        <item>Using Algebra to Solve Geometry Problems</item>
    </string-array>




    <string-array name="subtopic_names_11">
        <item>The Coordinate Plane</item>
        <item>Linear Equations</item>
        <item>Slope and Intercepts</item>
        <item>Multiplying and Dividing Monomials</item>
        <item>Factoring</item>
        <item>Trigonometric Ratios</item>
        <item>Quadratic Equations</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="subtopic_content_11">
        <item>The Coordinate Plane</item>
        <item>Linear Equations</item>
        <item>Slope and Intercepts</item>
        <item>Multiplying and Dividing Monomials</item>
        <item>Factoring</item>
        <item>Trigonometric Ratios</item>
        <item>Quadratic Equations</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="examples_11">
        <item>The Coordinate Plane</item>
        <item>Linear Equations</item>
        <item>Slope and Intercepts</item>
        <item>Multiplying and Dividing Monomials</item>
        <item>Factoring</item>
        <item>Trigonometric Ratios</item>
        <item>Quadratic Equations</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="citations_11">
        <item>The Coordinate Plane</item>
        <item>Linear Equations</item>
        <item>Slope and Intercepts</item>
        <item>Multiplying and Dividing Monomials</item>
        <item>Factoring</item>
        <item>Trigonometric Ratios</item>
        <item>Quadratic Equations</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>